[
    {
        "question": "What is 15 + 7?",
        "answer": "22",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 28 + 14?",
        "answer": "42",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 32 + 18?",
        "answer": "50",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 37 + 25?",
        "answer": "62",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 40 + 13?",
        "answer": "53",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 12 + 9?",
        "answer": "21",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 18 + 19?",
        "answer": "37",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 23 + 26?",
        "answer": "49",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 31 + 11?",
        "answer": "42",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 22 + 15?",
        "answer": "37",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    }
]
